Hi, I'm Bruce Davey, and I'm here with my longtime collaborator Larry Peterson.
And  we're going to be teaching you this course on "Introduction to Magma".
My background is... I'm a networking person from way back over 30 years in the networking industry,
and for about the last 10 years, I've been involved in software defined networking and worked on some source projects.
I'm really excited to be involved in the Magma project and I think you're going to find a lot of interesting technology in this project.
Let me just hand it over to Larry to introduce himself.
Yeah, thanks Bruce. Yeah, we go back many years, and I've been working mostly in universities on research projects related to the internet and cloud technologies.
The last few years I've been with the Open Networking Foundation and we're working on open source software,
both at the edge cloud, and a lot of the different access technologies, passive optical networks, 4G, 5G...
and so, Magma really brings all of that together. And I'm looking forward to telling you all about it.
Thanks, Larry. So, I think this is going to be a great course. We've really enjoyed getting involved in this project.
We think it has enormous potential to drive forward the open source approaches to mobile networking,
and you'll find out lots more about it in the upcoming material.
So, I hope you find it useful and enjoyable!